Hello friends, you are very welcome to Trading Date.
Friends, in this video
we are going to talk about a stock
named General Insurance and
how the stock can gain momentum in the coming time.
I will tell you in detail about this.
Watch the video till the end. Friends, the
video is going to be very informative.
First of all, if you see, this
stock is standing around its important level.
If we talk about the important level,
where I am feeling that friends, the
probability of the stock moving is very high. If we
talk about the important level from 11, then the
level is exactly the area of ​​145. The
area from 140 to 145, this is a
complete zone. This is a very important
zone and from here, the probability of the stock moving
in an upset is very high.
If I talk about the previous,
friends, this is about the tracking level. I
explain in every video about the traffic level. Here you will see what all is
shown in the stop, a rejection,
after that as soon as the stock is taken out above it,
friends, here  But you guys
will see how I took it up and created
momentum in it, after that if I
show you guys here, if you guys
see exactly what happened in the stock, sorry, did
it break down,
what is the stock doing after the breakdown, right now if you guys are
consolidating here, after that
what did the stock do, it broke out of the level again,
came above the level again and now
it is testing the level,
look at this huge candle, do not panic after seeing it
because if I talk to you about PVS,
you guys will see the green volume and the
red volume, the volume
is very low and I am feeling that the red volume is
very low friends and
what will the stock do in the coming time, I too will take the
support of this level,
taking the support of this level, you guys can see an upward
momentum continuing,
I am telling you guys again, yes,
this stock can give you very good returns,
previously also I had given the stock to you guys,
if we talk about my stock, it was around the price of 140  I had
given it to you friends and our near
target was around the price of 196200,
within a month we had captured this much target,
I will show you the previous
video, so you can go and watch it on
my channel, this is my channel,
you should subscribe to it and the previous
video that I had posted here, you
can search for General Insurance and see which video it is and in which
I had targeted you,
now if you will watch it, then exactly what I do
here is I will
put the chart of weekly time frame
and here if you will
see exactly, here you have to
support reversal within the smaller time frame,
here you will see
what has happened here friends, the inverted timer
and one is two one, it means friends this
is the decision point and where it is divided,
what is the sign of 2G, friends reversal
reversal happens here also, there is 2G
form there, so here exactly what
you have done at the important level  The stock that
I am getting around and I
will think about it in the bank segment here because the stock
gives very good returns and is a government company,
friends, I do not think there is
any risk in this stock right now if you guys will see then
no friend brother, it is going to top around the price of 132
and I am going to keep the target a little longer
friends because this time friends,
this stock was
not able to clear the previous register,
right now if you guys see then you can easily see
what the stock will do taking the support of this level, the
momentum is visible to you people, so
I will convert it in the monthly time frame
and here if you guys are
thinking in terms of the target inside it,
friends, if you will see the target inside it then the
first target is going to be ours, the first
target is going to be ours, this is the level
friends, the area of ​​₹200 was activated here previously
where the ceiling was
activated, I will bring the target down a little, the target is going to be
ours, the target is going to be near by
190 area a little inside the buffer,
we will plan the second target in the big way to get out from inside it  So
friends, I am going to keep the second target a little
inside this and a little near buy. The
entire Nearby 225 area is going to be
like a second target
and I can also take this stock to
a good side by breaking it out.
Previously, if I
show you guys a train line, friends,
why am I getting into a wine mood from within this,
if you guys look here,
you will see, did it break
out of the train line exactly? Did it break out of the train line
exactly?
How many times did it test the train line?
You will see, the first time it tested like this, the
second time it tested here, if we talk about the
third time, then it
tested exactly that way and the fourth time friends,
you will see, it broke out and
tested it. Now friends, what will this stock do, it will gain
immense sideways momentum from here,
so I will think around this level in the bank's big.
Talking about the target,
friends, I am going to keep the target a little bigger
within it, till here the target is going to be
ours. The Nearby 225
area is ours.  It is going to stay inside it like a target, so
what I do is right now I am
putting a small tractor inside it and the position will be visible properly,
exactly you will see, so here I will
tell you again that
our entry point will be
around the price of 145, talk about the target of Staff Nurse, the
first target is going to be around the price of 190,
talk about the second target, the independent target is
around the price of 224 and the top loss
is very small, friends, 131 means 7% of the
stock is 50%, this stock will definitely take,
friends, I feel that in the coming time the
stock will move from here and I have brought this type of
information video on my channel daily, after
analyzing you people, I
tell you how
you people have to think here and how to find out,
after that friends, I
provide you the early morning Nifty over, so
you people can watch, learn, understand and
subscribe to the channel, friends,
I bring content for you.  I am here, see you
in the next video, Jai Hind